Meet Oakland's Newest Battle Rapper.
Bodied is a drama, comedy, music film directed by Joseph Kahn.
A progressive graduate student finds success and sparks outrage when his interest
in battle rap as a thesis subject becomes a competitive obsession.
Adam, played by Calum Worthy.
Behn Grymm, played by Jackie Long.
Maya, played by Rory Uphold.
Prospek, played by Jonnie Park.
Che Corleone, played by Walter Perez.
Devine Write, played by Shoniqua Shandai.
Bodied is a 2017 American battle rap comedy-drama film directed by Joseph Kahn, written by
Alex Larsen and produced by Eminem, his manager Paul Rosenberg, and Adi Shankar.
The film premiered at the 2017 Toronto International Film Festival.
It stars Calum Worthy as Adam, a graduate student who becomes a competitive battle rapper after
becoming immersed in the scene while working on his graduate thesis on the subject.
At the Toronto International Film Festival, the film won the Toronto
International Film Festival People's Choice Award: Midnight Madness.
It also won Fantastic Fest's 2017 Audience Award.
In January 2018, YouTube Red announced it had acquired exclusive streaming rights,
with a limited theatrical release beginning on November 2, 2018.
Upon the film's release, it received generally positive reviews from critics who
praised its humour and meaningful exploration of certain dark themes.
The film explores themes of rap music, hip-hop, cat, college, thesis.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.